<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Code Challenge Intent</string>
    <string name="button_main">Text One</string>
    <string name="activity2_name">Text One</string>
    <string name="article_title">Beatles Anthology Vol. 1</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Behind That Locked Door: Beatles Rarities!</string>
    <string name="article_text">In a vault deep inside Abbey Road Studios in London - protected by an unmarked, triple-locked, police-alarmed door - are something like 400 hours of unreleased Beatles recordings, starting from June 2, 1962 and ending with the very last tracks recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album. The best of the best were released by Apple Records in the form of the 3-volume Anthology series.
        For more information, see the Beatles Time Capsule at www.rockument.com.
    \n\n
    This volume starts with the first new Beatle song, "Free as a Bird" (based on a John Lennon demo, found only on <i>The Lost Lennon Tapes Vol. 28</i>, and covers the very earliest historical recordings, outtakes from the first albums, and live recordings from early concerts and BBC Radio sessions.
    \n\n
    <b><i>Cry for a Shadow</i></b> - Many a Beatle fanatic started down the outtake road, like I did, with a first listen to this song. Originally titled “Beatle Bop” and recorded in a single session that yielded four songs (the other three featured Tony Sheridan with the Beatles as a backing band), “Cry for a Shadow” is an instrumental written by Lennon and Harrison, which makes it unique to this day. John Lennon plays rhythm guitar, George Harrison plays lead guitar, Paul McCartney plays bass, and Pete Best plays drums. The sessions were produced by Bert Kaempfert in Hamburg, Germany, during the Beatles’ second visit from April through July of 1961 to play in the Reeperbahn-section clubs.
    \n\n
    <b><i>My Bonnie</i></b> and <b><i>Ain’t She Sweet</i></b> — At the same session, the Beatles played on “My Bonnie” (the first-ever single with Beatles playing), as the backing band for English singer Tony Sheridan, originally a member of the Jets. The popularity of this single in Liverpool brought the Beatles to the attention of Brian Epstein, who worked in the NEMS record store and tried to meet demand for the disc. John Lennon then sings a fine “Ain’t She Sweet” (his first-ever released vocal).
    \n\n
    <b><i>Searchin</i></b> — A Jerry Leiber - Mike Stoller comedy song that was a hit for the Coasters in 1957, and a popular live favorite of the Beatles. The Coasters also had a hit with “Besame Mucho” and the Beatles covered that song as well. Ringo Starr had by now replaced Pete Best on drums. The high falsetto is George, who also plays a hesitant lead guitar. This is from their first audition for Decca Records in London on Jan 1., 1962, live in the studio. The Grateful Dead would later cover “Searchin” with a similar arrangement, Pigpen doing the Paul vocals. A live version is available on outtake records featuring the Dead joined by the Beach Boys!
    \n\n
    <b><i>Love Me Do</i></b> — An early version of the song, played a bit slower and with more of a blues feeling, and a cool bossa-nova beat in middle. Paul had to sing while John played harmonica — a first for the group. Pete Best played drums on this version.
    \n\n
    <b><i>She Loves You – Till There Was You – Twist and Shout</i></b> — Live at the Princess Wales Theatre by Leicester Square in London, attended by the Queen. “Till There Was You” (by Meredith Wilson) is from the musical The Music Man and a hit for Peggy Lee in 1961. Before playing it, Paul said it was recorded by his favorite American group, “Sophie Tucker” (which got some laughs). At the end, John tells the people in the cheaper seats to clap their hands, and the rest to “rattle your jewelry” and then announces “Twist and Shout” (a song by Bert Russell and Phil Medley that was first recorded in 1962 by the Isley Brothers). A film of the performance shows the Queen smiling at John’s remark.
    \n\n
    <b><i>Leave My Kitten Alone</i></b> — One of the lost Beatle songs recorded during the “Beatles For Sale” sessions but never released. This song, written by Little Willie John, Titus Turner, and James McDougal, was a 1959 R&amp;B hit for Little Willie John and covered by Johnny Preston before the Beatles tried it and shelved it. A reference to a “big fat bulldog” may have influenced John’s “Hey Bulldog” (Yellow Submarine album), which is a similar rocker.
    \n\n
    <b><i>One After 909</i></b> — A song recorded for the <i>Let It Be</i> album was actually worked on way back in the beginning, six years earlier. This take shows how they did it much more slowly, with an R&amp;B feel to it.</string>

    <string name="button_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="activity3_name">Text Two</string>
    <string name="text_artikel">
        <b><i>Once upon a time</i></b>, there lived a fisherman with his family in the coastal area of West Sumatra. That little family consist of the fisherman, his wife and his son. The name of his son was Malin Kundang. They have lived in poverty for a long time. One day the fisherman decided to sail to a new world hoping that he will find his fortune and change the life of his family. Months passed by but there was no news from the fisherman and after more than a year the fisherman was still not returning to his hometown.
    \n\n
        With the help of Malin Kundang, his mother started to work in order to fulfill their daily need. Luckily, Malin Kundang was a smart and diligent boy so he always try to lighten the burden of his mother. But he was also a bit naughty. There was once a day where Malin was chasing a chicken and he accidentally stumbled on a rock and he injured his right arm leaving a permanent scratch mark on it.
    \n\n
        When he was older, he decided to be a ship’s crew so that he can sail to a new place and find his fortune so he can make her mother happy with his wealth that he earned from his trip. He got this idea when he saw a ship captain that was once a poor man now had became a very wealthy man after he came back from his trip. When he had made up his mind, he told his mother about his plan. His mother disagree with his idea, but Malin kept forcing his mother to allow him to go. Finally his mother gave him her permission.
    \n\n
        The next day, after preparing for some supplies, Malin and his mother went to the pier where the ship was waiting for him. He said good bye to his mother and his mother told him to never forget her and to return when he had became a successful man. She let Malin go with tears in her eyes. They waved their hand to each other as the ship moved away from the pier until it couldn’t be seen anymore.
    \n\n
        Malin Kundang spent his time on the ship learning about sailorship from some senior ship’s crew. Unfortunately, the ship was attacked by pirates in the middle of the sea. All merchandise on the ship was raided by the pirates. The pirates also killed most of the ship’s crew. Malin Kundang was safe because during the attack, he hid in a small secret chamber of the ship. When the pirates had acquired all valuable stuff from the ship, they went away and left the ship to sink.
    \n\n
        The ship was drifted to the shore. Malin Kundang was the only survivor from the ship. He was so tired but he forced himself to walk and search for the nearest village. When he arrived at the nearest village, the villagers helped him and give him some food and water. After that, Malin Kundang told them the story about the ship and the pirates. The villagers took pity on him so they helped him to start a live in their village.
    \n\n
        The soil in the village was very fertile so Malin Kundang decided to start his own farm. He worked diligently on his farm every day. Day by day he became even more wealthy. With knowledge that he acquired during his time on his old ship, he started to buy some ship and build his own fleet with more than 100 employee. As soon as he became a rich man, he wedded a very beautiful girl in the village.
    \n\n
        The story of Malin Kundang who had became a wealthy man spread across the ocean until it was heard by his mother in his hometown. His mother was so happy and grateful to hear the news that her son had became a successful man. Ever since she heard the news, Malin Kundang’s mother went to the pier every day hoping that she can see it right away when Malin Kundang returned to the village. But, Malin Kundang was never showed up.
    \n\n
        Years have passed since the first time the news reach Malin Kundang’s hometown. One day, Malin and his wife decided to go on a sea voyage with their large and beautiful ship. One of the place that they visited was Malin’s hometown. Malin Kundang’s mother who kept showing up at the pier every day quickly recognized her son who was standing on the ship’s deck with a beautiful woman. She became even more certain that it was Malin Kundang when she saw the scratch mark on his right arm.
    \n\n
        Malin Kundang’s mother run toward Malin Kundang and hug him. “Malin Kundang, my son, I miss you so much, why didn’t you sent any news all this time? I’ve been waiting for you” she said. Instead of hugging his mother, Malin Kundang pushed the old woman backward until she fell to the ground. “Who are you?” said Malin Kundang pretending that he didn’t recognize his mother, “I don’t know you!” he yelled at her. “I’m your mother Malin, have you forgotten me, son?” asked his mother. “Is this really your mother Malin?” asked his wife. “No, absolutely not. She was just a beggar who pretended to be my mother so she can get my treasure” he said. Malin Kundang’s mother was very angry to hear what he said, she raised her hand and pray to God, “Oh god, my heart was so hurt, if he really is my son, i cursed him into a stone” she said. Not long after that, a storm came and destroyed Malin’s ship, after that Malin Kundang’s body slowly turned into coral.
    \n\n
        Source : https://www.bigbanktheories.com/contoh-narrative-text-malin-kundang-lengkap-dengan-artinya/
    </string>
    <string name="subtitle_artikel"><b>Folk legends from the province of West Sumatera</b></string>
    <string name="judul_artikel">Malin Kundang</string>

    <string name="button_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="activity4_name">Text Three</string>
    <string name="judul_article">Bawang Merah Bawang Putih</string>
    <string name="subtitle_article"><b>Folk legend from the province of Riau</b></string>
    <string name="text_article">
        <b><i>Once upon a time</i></b>, there lived a widow with a beautiful daughter and a beautiful stepdaughter. Her daughter’s name is Bawang Merah and her stepdaughter’s name is Bawang Putih. Her husband, Bawang Putih’s biological father, had passed away a long time ago. The three of them live in a small village.
    \n\n
        The widow was not a nice lady. She treated Bawang Putih very badly. She made Bawang Putih to do all the chores such as doing the laundry, serving the meal, cleaning the house, keeping the weter supply and many more. Her daughter, Bawang Merah, is just like her. She is lazy, arrogant, greedy and envious. She treated Bawang Putih as a house maid for her. Whereas Bawang Putih is the opposite of her stepsister. She is humble, unpretentious, diligent, honest and kind hearted. She always follow her stepmother’s instruction without complaining.
    \n\n
        <b><i>One day</i></b>, Bawang Putih was doing the laundry at the river bank. She was too busy cleaning the clothes that she didn’t realize that one of her stepmother’s favorite clothes fell into the river and drifted away. By the time she had finished the laundry, she realized that there was a missing clothes. She tried to look for it anywhere, but she couldn’t find it. She was so worried, because she knew that her stepmother will be very angry when she found out that her favorite clothes was missing.
    \n\n
        Bawang Putih decided to follow the river flow hoping that she will find the lost clothes. Every time she met someone near the river, she would asked them about the clothes, but no one saw it until she met a fisherman who claimed to have seen it floating in front oh him a while ago. The fisherman told Bawang Putih to chase it, because he believed that the clothes must be not far from there. Bawang Putih thanked the fisherman and continue her search.
    \n\n
        Bawang Putih kept walking at the river bank until she saw that there is an intersection of the river that flow into a cave. She entered the cave and she found out that there is an old woman living in the cave alone. Bawang Putih asked to the old woman about the missing clothes. It turned out that the old woman found it in front of the cave and kept it. Bawang Putih asked the old woman to return the clothes to her and she explained that it was her stepmother’s favorite clothes and she will be angry if Bawang Putih didn’t bring it back.
    \n\n
        The old woman agreed to return the clothes but she asked Bawang Putih to help her to cook and to clean the place. Bawang Putih agreed with the old woman request. She started to cook and after that she cleaned the cave, the job was easy for her because she did it every day at home. The old woman was satisfied with the result and she gave back the clothes to Bawang Putih. She also offered her two pumpkin as a reward for her help. Bawang Putih chose the small one. After that, Bawang Putih thanked the old woman and went back to her house.
    \n\n
        When Bawang Putih arrived at her house, her stepmother and her stepsister was mad at her because she came home late. Bawang Putih tried to explain everything to them but they became more angry because she only brought a small pumpkin. Her stepmother took the pumpkin from her and throw it to the floor. The pumpkin shattered and a lot of jewelry made of gold and diamond came out of the pumpkin. All of them were surprised. The stepmother collected all of the jewelry right away. She became even more upset after that because Bawang Putih chose to bring the small pumpkin instead of the big one.
    \n\n
        The next day, Bawang Merah and her mother planned to recreate the situation experienced by Bawang Putih yesterday. Bawang Merah throw a clothes on purpose into the river and let it drifted away. She followed it until she reached the cave where the old woman live. The old woman gave her the same request as she gave to Bawang Putih yesterday, but Bawang Merah refuse it and she insisted the old woman to handed over to her the big pumpkin. The old woman gave the pumpkin to her.
    \n\n
        Bawang Merah rushed back to her house when she received the pumpkin from the old woman. When she arrived at home her mother was waiting for her in front of the house. They couldn’t wait any longer to open the pumpkin and collect the jewelry inside it. They smashed the pumpkin to the floor, but it was not jewelry coming out of the pumpkin, instead a lot of snakes crawled out of the pumpkin. The snake was about to attack them when suddenly Bawang Putih came out from the house and attacked the snake by using a broom. The snakes fled and they were save.
    \n\n
        Bawang Merah and her mother regretted their actions and apologize to Bawang Putih. They realized their mistake and promised that they will never treat Bawang Putih like they used to. Bawang Putih forgave them and they all live happily after that.
    \n\n
        Source : https://www.bigbanktheories.com/contoh-narrative-text-bawang-merah-bawang-putih-dan-artinya/
    </string>

</resources>